just shoot for the stars,If it feels right
射下星星，如果这样感觉不错
And then from my heart, If you feel like
然后摘取我心，如果你愿意
You take me away
你带我离开
You make it okay
因你让这一切变美好
I swear I’ll behave
我发誓我会安分守己
You wanted control
你曾想要控制
So we waited
所以我们等待
I put on a show
我总是在演出
Now we’re naked
但现在赤诚相待
You say I’m a kid
你说我是一个孩子
My ego is bare
自尊又好胜
I don’t give a shit! And it goes like this
但我不在乎了，所以就这样吧
Take me by the tongue, And I’ll know you
抚慰我吧，让我更了解你
Kiss me til you’re drunk and I’ll show you
吻我吧，直到你也沉醉其中
You wanna move like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the moo o ves like jagger
你失控，我失控
I don’t need to try and control you
而我不需要试着去控制你
Look into my eyes and I’ll hold you
看着我的眼睛吧，当我抱着你
With the moves like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the moo o
你失控，我失控
Well maybe it’s hard
是的，也许这很困难
When you feel like You’re broken and scarred
当你觉得你受到了伤害
It feels right
但是你会感觉好起来的
When you’re with me
当你和我在一起
I’ll make you believe
我会让你坚信
I’ve got the key
我有神奇之钥
Oh, so get in the car, You can ride it,Oh
我们进车里去吧，今天你可以开
Wherever you want Get inside it
无论你想要去哪里，交由你决定
If you wanna steer
如果你想要掌舵
I’m shifting gears
我就立刻换你
I’ll take it from here
从现在就开始
And it goes like this…
所以就这样吧
Take me by the tongue, And I’ll know you
抚慰我吧，让我更了解你
Kiss me til you’re drunk and I’ll show you
吻我吧，直到你也沉醉其中
You wanna move like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the mooo ves like jagger
你失控，我失控
I don’t need to try and control you
而我不需要试着去控制你
Look into my eyes and I’ll hold you
看着我的眼睛吧，当我抱着你
With the moves like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the m ooo ves like jagger
你失控，我失控
You wanna know,how to make me smile
你想要知道如何逗我笑？
Take control on me just for the night
这个夜晚你来掌控大局
When I share my secret, You’re gonna have to keep it
你要保守和你分享的秘密
Nobody else can see this
没有人可以知道
So watch and learn I won't show you twice
所以为什么不呢？
Head to toe
从头到尾，原原本本
ooh baby roll me right
我要说给你听
But if i share my secret, You’re gonna have to keep it
你要保守和你分享的秘密
Nobody else can see this
没有人可以知道
Oh! And it goes like this…
所以就这样吧
Take me by the tongue, And I’ll know you
抚慰我吧，让我更了解你
Kiss me til you’re drunk and I’ll show you
吻我吧，直到你也沉醉其中
You wanna move like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the moo o ves like jagger
你失控，我失控
I don’t need to try and control you
而我不需要试着去控制你
Look into my eyes and I’ll hold you
看着我的眼睛吧，当我抱着你
You wanna move like jagger, I've got the moves like jagger
I've got the mo  come on say
你失控，我失控   一起唱
o oo oo oo oo oo oo oo oo ves like jagger
我们一起失控